

Gerrard St E, Toronto, ON M4M 1Y3, Canada

+1 856 599 8990

Summary

Senior Full Stack | Blockchain developer with 8+ years of rich experience in web development. With my rich experience in web development, my skill set includes:

- HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Tailwind CSS
- Javascript | TypeScript | ¡Query
- PHP | Laravel | Codeigniter | Wordpress | Magento
- Liquid template | Shopify frontend
- Nodejs | Reactjs | Nextjs | Vuejs | Nuxtjs | Expressjs | Nestjs
- SQL | MySQL | PostgreSQL | OracleDB | MongoDB | Firebase
- GraphQL
- Web3js | Solidity
- AWS | Docker | Git

As a Senior Full stack | Blockchain developer, I can provide perfect code results based on your requirement. I am always looking for long term relationships based on trust and professionalism.

Work experience

Blockchain developer | Technical Supporter

2022/02 - Current

Yield Dank (New York, United State

Working as a Technical supporter for this team.

Part time project

Senior Nodejs | PHP developer

2021/02 - 2022/01

Zoopr (Dubai, United Arab Emirates)

Implement real time communication module for website.

This project was built by Codeigniter. With PHP language's limitation, it is hard to make real time communication module for this project. So I have made it using Websocket which communicate with Nodejs Server. Also beautified codes all across the project.

Used skills:

- Codeigniter
- Nodejs
- Websocket
- MySQL
- PHP
- Javascript
- Ajax

Senior Full Stack | Blockchain developer

2020/06 - 2020/11

Neon Skies (New York, United States)

Build NFT website and smart contract for NeonSkies team.

- Built front pages using Reactjs
- Made Discord validation Bot for Marketplace channel.
- Create Smart Contract functionalities which include Minting and Staking functionalities.

- Unit test for code quality
- Using GraphQL for data response.
- Integrate APIs
- Maintain website for 5 months.

Web3 | Solidity developer

2019/10 - 2020/04

Vault3D (Amsterdam Havens, North Holland, Netherlands)

Create 2 NFT website with this agency end to end.

- Built Front pages using Reactjs.
- Made web3js code for connecting several wallets to the website.
- Create Smart Contract functionalities which contains Minting, Staking functions.
- Make site mobile friendly with Tailwind CSS.

Senior Full Stack | Ecommerce developer

2018/03 - 2019/07

Vyudu Agency (New York, United States)

I was working as a Senior Full Stack | Ecommerce developer in this agency. During this period, I was working with SPA frameworks such as Reactjs, Vuejs, Nextjs, and Nuxtjs and also used E-commerce frameworks such as Magento and Shopify.

I have built 20+ web projects using SPA frameworks and 30+ E-commerce shops using Magento and Shopify. Used Skills and Experience:

- Built more than 20 websites using SPA frameworks such as Reactjs, Vuejs, Nextjs and Nuxtjs.
- Laravel and Nodejs used as a backend framework
- GraphQL and AWS
- Firebase, MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL and Oracle
- 3rd Party APIs integration
- Docker environment
- Git | Github | Jira | Agile
- Built E-commerce websites from PSD or Figma design using Magento, Woocommerce and Shopify frameworks.
- Made custom extensions such as "Search Product by Model", "Buy Products by Attribute", "Presale", ... for Magento framework.
- Made custom plugins for woocommerce shop

Senior Full Stack developer

2016/10 - 2018/05

Velox Agency (New York, United States)

As a progressive developer, I have learned javascript frameworks such as Nodejs, Reactjs, Vuejs, Nextjs, Nuxtjs, Nestjs, and Expressjs. I was working as a full-stack developer in this agency. I have built 30+ web projects using js frameworks. Also, I used MongoDB, firebase,docker, GraphQL, and AWS services.

Senior E-commerce developer

2015/09 - 2017/02

PERCEPTIVELY LLC (London, England, United Kingdom)

Built E-commerce Stores from PSD or Figma design.

Used Skills and Experience

- PHP | Liquid template
- Javascript | jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Magento, Woocommerce, Shopify
- Magento custom extension development
- Wordpress custom plugin development.
- Build custom theme from PSD or Figma design (Magento, Wordpress, Shopify)
- Magento 1.x to Magento 2.x migration

- Magento to Shopify migration
- Magento to Woocommerce migration
- Speed optimization using GTmetrix

I have built 50+ ecommerce websites using Magento and Woocommerce framework.

Senior PHP developer

2014/10 - 2015/08

Palmer Creative (London, England, United Kingdom)

I started work as an intern in this agency. I have built 20+ websites using PHP frameworks such as Laravel, Codeigniter, Wordpress and Magento. In the end of this period, I was a Senior Lead developer. It was taken only 1 year for me.

Education

Master of Computer Application

2011/05 - 2014/08

Tsinghua University, China

In this period, I have learned about computer science from talented professors. With the professors' effort, my skills have been highly improved. I am proud of my computer skills with the name of my university.

Featured Projects

Montana Wood Work Magento Shop

2018/05 - 2018/09

Montana Wood Work

This is an E-Commerce project that has been built by Magento 2. I have built this project end-end. Used Skills and Experience

- PHP | Magento 2.3
- Javascript | jQuery | requireJS
- Google recaptcha api integration
- Payment integration
- PSD to Magento 2
- Bootstrap
- Develop custom extension for this store
- o Layered Navigation filter extension
- o Swatch extension
- Optimize speed over 85 on GTmetrix

Zoopr Project 2021/02 - 2022/01

Zoopr

This project was built by Codeigniter and Javascript. I have made 3 main modules that use the WebSocket service. Also, I have beautified codes all across the project. That was messy before. After that, I made contract codes and wallet connections using web3js.

Used Skills and Experience

- Made real time chat module using WebSocket and Nodejs
- Made real time notification module using WebSocket
- Integrate APIs for getting cryptocurrencies and NFT data
- Beautify codes
- Made smart contract using Solidity

Neon Skies NFT website

2020/06 - 2020/11

Neon Skies

Neon Skies is one of my best DAPP projects. It has been built using Reactjs and Web3js. Contract code contains minting, staking, and swap functionalities. Also this project uses AWS Lamda service and GraphQL.

Used Skills and Experience

- Figma to Reactis web application
- Integrate wallet to web application using web3js
- Deploy project to AWS instance
- Create smart contract code using Solidity
- Get data by GraphQL
- Integrate Restful API
- Make web application bug free
- Test site using rinkeby testnet.

FamilyTree365 Nuxtjs(vuejs) Project

2018/06 - 2018/08

Vyudu Agency

This was a family tree project which uses nuxtjs as a frontend framework and Laravel as a backend framework. Customers can make their family tree on the dashboard. I have built this project from end to end. It takes 3 months for completion.

Also this project uses GraphQL for data response.

Used Skills and Experience:

- Build front pages from figma design using Nuxtjs
- Build backend using Laravel
- Integrate payments
- Integrate APIs
- Tailwind CSS
- Using GraphQL for data response
- Github
- Docker
- Ubuntu

HourPrice Vuejs Project

2017/03 - 2017/05

Velox Agency

This project was built by Vuejs. I have built this project from end to end. It contains an hour pricing calculator which is similar to the Upwork app. It takes only 2 months for completion. Also this project uses AWS Lamda service.

Used Skills and Experience:

- Build front pages using Vuejs
- AWS S3 service
- Integrate MailChimp
- Amazon Cloudfront
- Payment integration

Scarlettwear Shopify Store

2016/04 - 2016/05

Perceptively LLC

This store has been built by shopify. It takes only 1 month for completion. I have built front pages from figma design.

Muzzle loaders Magento Store

2014/11 - 2015/02

Palmer Creative

I have built this store from PSD design. This store contains 6 custom modules and 4 payment gateways. This has been taken 3 months for completion.

Blockchain

As a new era's web developer, I have 3 years of experience with blockchain development. I have built several NFT market places using React, Vue and Web3js. With my experience, I am good at smart contract development with Solidity.

Database

With my 10+ years of computer programming experience, I am very familiar with several kind of database management systems such as Oracle, Mysql, Postgresql, Mongodb and Firebase.

Javascript

As a senior full stack developer, I have 6 years of rich experience in working with javascript frameworks such as React, Vue, Nuxt, Next, Express, Node. Also I am very familiar with using Typescript.

PHP

With my 8 years of rich experience in php development, I have built 50+ web projects using PHP frameworks such as Laravel, Codeigniter and Zend.

Created with 📅 VisualCV